Guide to the Noted Women Collection, 1884-1939
Department of Special Collections
Noted Women Collection,
1884-1939
Special Collections M131
18 items
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions:
None.
Provenance:
Gifts and purchases from various sources.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
This collection consists of single items, autographs, and small collections of noted women, American and foreign.
CONTAINER LIST
- Adams, Jane [1860-1935] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - T.L.S. & cvr. to Mrs. M.C. Sloss, 1915 Apr. 9
  - T.L.S. & cvr. to Mrs. M.C. Sloss, 1915 July 23
- Anthony, Susan Brownell [1820-1906] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A.L.S. to Mrs. McLeash & Mrs. Snook, 1897 Jan. 11
- Autographs (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lucretia Radolph Garfield (Mrs. James A.) [1832-1918], 1884 Mar. 14
  - Mrs. John Alexander Logan (Mary Simmerson Cunningham) [1838-1923], 1887 Mar. 28
- Coolidge, Grace Anna (Mrs. Calvin) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A.L.S. to Mrs. Sloss, 1932 Aug. 11
- Coulter, Edith M. (Box 1, Folder 4a)
  - A.N.S., n.d.
- Hoover, Lou Henry [1874-1944] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1. A.N.S. & cvr. to Mrs. Sloss, 1928 June 16
  - 2. T.L.S. & cvr. to Mrs. Sloss, 1932 Oct. 18
  - 3. Clipping, 1932 Oct. 18
  - 4. T.L.S. to Mrs. Sloss, 1934 Nov. 21
- Keller, Helen Adams (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - T.L.S. to R. L. Wilbur, 1930 Dec. 20
- Key, Ellen Karoline Sofia [1849-1926] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A.L.S. & cvr. to the Women's Board of the Panama Pacific International Exposition, 1914 July 27
- Longworth, Alice Roosevelt (Mrs. Nicholas) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A.L.S. to R. L. Wilbur, 1932 Nov. 17
- Roosevelt, Anna Eleanor (Mrs. F. D.) [1884-1962] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - T.L.S. to R. L. Wilbur, 1939 Feb. 23
- Roosevelt, [Sara Delano] (Mrs. James) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - T.L.S. to Motion Picture Research Council, 1935 June 3
- Taft, Helen Herron (Mrs. W. H.) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A.L.S. to Mrs. Snook, 1930 Mar. 14
- Watson, Elizabeth Lowe (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - T.L.S. to Mrs. Snook, 1910 Oct. 17
  - T.L.S. to Mrs. Snook, 1910 Sept. 24